http://www.myshareadvantage.com/internet-privacy

LoginMy AccountsSavings optionsShare in the advantages of savingFREE CheckingShare in the advantages of FREE checkingReorder ChecksInvestment CalculatorMy Loans Credit CardsNOW available in 3 feature options VehicleCruise the country with low rates on new and used autos Recreational VehicleGet outdoors and back to nature with our great rates MortgageNew, refinance, remodel! Home advantages with Share Advantage SpecialsSee our current loan specialsPayment CalculatorOnline Access login for Credit Card uChoose Rewards loginMy Credit Union SOFTWARE CONVERSIONHow will it effect you?VIDEOS & CLICK-THRU DEMOsA growing library of our new products RatesSharing the advantages of great ratesEventsAnnual events and important dates About UsHow we came to be Share AdvantageLocationsInformation and hours for our locationsNEWSLETTERMembershipHow to JoinCost Recovery Fee ScheduleContactCommunityOnline Banking Login1-888-722-5931Internet PrivacyYour privacy is important to us.This Online Privacy Statement is intended to provide information about how we treat information that you provide to us through the Share Advantage Credit Union ("SACU") website ("Site"). Any use of the Site constitutes your consent to this statement.
BrowsingAs you visit our Site, our web server does not recognize information regarding your e-mail address but does recognize what browser you are using. We currently collect aggregate information about the use of our Site that does not personally identify you. We reserve the right to change this Statement from time to time.
E-MailVarious parts of our Site allow you to submit information to us via e-mail. By doing so you are actively participating and giving the credit union permission to access the information. We collect the e-mail addresses of those who send us e-mail and the information provided in the e-mail.
Use of InformationIf we deal with information that is subject to laws requiring us to make certain disclosures or take other actions, we will make the disclosure or take the action in connection with the particular information or service, and those disclosures are additional to this Statement. In general, SACU does not sell its membership list and does not share with third parties private information that you submit which personally identifies you. There are several exceptions to this general rule, which include, but are not limited to the following:When SACU cooperates with a third party to allow products or services to be made available to our membership, we typically share with that third party information necessary or advisable to provide the service or product. If our sharing agreement has additional terms or conditions, we will make the required disclosures in connection with the particular product or service.Information submitted to obtain products or services is used by SACU and third parties as deemed necessary or advisable by SACU (or the third parties) to verify, provide, process and keep records or the requested service (including services that are incidental to the requested service) and our experience with you. We also combine that information with other information to determine your identity or eligibility.In order to comply with government agency or court orders SACU endeavors to notify its members of such requests unless prohibited by court order or law to do so.We use information in order to verify the existence and condition of your account for a third party, such as a credit bureau or merchant.SACU reserves the right to use the information to protect itself, its members or third parties and to process insurance and other claims. We also use personal information to identify you, communicate with you, and to help us respond to or deal with questions or concerns.SACU may send (or arrange for others to send) e-mails regarding surveys, focus-groups, promotions, and products and services offered by SACU or third parties which we believe might be of interest. If you do not want to receive those communications in the future, please contact us at 218.722.5931.
Storage of InformationSubject to applicable law, SACU will retain and use personal information, as appropriate in the the normal course of our business.Nothing in this Privacy Statement affects our ability to collect, combine, use, verify, retain, and report, including sharing with our regulators, information submitted in connection with the provision of products and services. We also reserve the right to do the same with information obtained from public sources or third parties, and other information that does not personally identify you, without reference to this Online Privacy Statement. Main Office2502 Maple Grove Rd. Duluth, MN 55811 Phone(218) 722-5931Fax218-740-3080 Map Essentia Office407 E 3rd St. Suite 0210Duluth, MN 55805 Phone(218) 740-2244Fax218-786-7229 Map West Duluth Office4918 Grand Ave.Duluth, MN 55807 Phone(218) 740-2222Fax218-740-2255 Map 2018 Share Advantage Credit Union.
All Rights Reserved.You are about to leave myshareadvantage.com.You are navigating to VISA's Online Access login for the Share Advantage VISA Credit Card at https://onlineaccessplus.com/oa/myshareadvantage/https://onlineaccessplus.com/oa/myshareadvantage/< Go backContinue on >You are about to leave myshareadvantage.com.You are navigating to VISA's uChoose Rewards website for the Advantage Rewards Credit Card at www.uchooserewards.com< Go backContinue on >SACU Mobile BankingMoneyPassCardValetSACU Mobile BankingMoneyPassCardValet
